Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Save Our Union Files (Box 11)
  - El Diario/La Prensa Editorial "Playing Turner's Game", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    May 21, 1985
  - Dissent "A New Turn at 1199" and "Bread & Roses, Crusts & Thorns", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    Summer 1986 and Spring 1986
  - Daily News/Times "Union Big Cited for Contempt" and "Court Threatens President", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Daily News "Union Head Faces Arrest" and "Health Care Union Probed", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    April 1, 1986 and March 28, 1986
  - News "Hospital Union in a Fit Trying on a Suit", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    4/7/86
  - The Daily News, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    4/8 "Correction" 4/11 "Union Leader Sues" 4/14 "Union Rebels Watchful" 4/15 "Days of Decision for Local 1199" 4/16 "Hospital Union Back in Court" 4/24 "Dissident Ousts Hosp-Union Head"
  - Daily News "Changes Due at Hospital Union", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - The Daily News, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - The Daily News Editorial "State of the Union", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - The Daily News "1199's Insurgents Appeal", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    Tuesday, May 20, 1986
  - Daily News 500 AD, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    6/2/86
  - Daily News Metro: "Hosp Union Leader to Step Down", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    Wednesday, June 25, 1986
  - Daily News "The Healing Process to Begin", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    Monday, June 30, 1986
  - Daily News "Single Mother" (Sonia Robinson), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    9/2/86
  - Daily News "Hospital Pay Hikes", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Amsterdam News "Turner's Foe Gets Backing" (Ossie Davis), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    4/12/86
  - N.Y. Amsterdam News "1199 Election Brouhaha", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    Saturday 5/31/86
  - Amsterdam News Editorial, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    Saturday, June 28, 1986
  - Amsterdam News "Turner's Days are Over", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Amsterdam News Editorial "1199 Popped Off by League?", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    10/4/86
  - City Sun "Union Head Charged with Embezzlement", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    April 9-15, 1986
  - The City Sun "Inquiry Snags Outcome of Union Election", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    5/7-13/86
  - City Sun Editorial, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    5/14-20/86
  - City Sun Editorial, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    May 21-27, 1986
  - City Sun Editorial, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    June 25 - July 1, 1986
  - City Sun "Union Leader is Booted Out", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - City Sun "Hospital Union Begins Contract Talks", 1986 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    9/3 - 9/86
  - "Heads", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - White Collar Report "Election Fraud" and "League", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    1/9/85 and 7/3/85
  - BNA/White Collar Report, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    July 31
  - Press Clips - Originals or Good Xerox, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - N.Y. Times, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - N.Y. Voice, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Village Voice, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - In These Times, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Daily News, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - The Nation "Turnergate at 1199", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    2/23/85
  - N.Y. Newsday, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - NY Newsday "Grand Jury Probes Hospital Union", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    March 29, 1985
  - N.Y. Post "I Helped My Union Boss" and "Hospital Hanky-Panky", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    1/7 and 1/12
  - Amsterdam News, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - City Sun, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Press, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Affidavit of Eddie Kay, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - News, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Press, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Articles and Clippings (Box 12)
  - Nursing Home Work, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fact Sheet - 1199 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Campaign '88, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - NY Times Labor-Jackson Connection in the City Strengthens Both, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Monday 4/18/88
  - NY Times/News of the Week "Unions Hope to Flex Old-Time Political Muscle in Primary", 1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    4/17/88
  - 1976 Strike (Box 12, Folder 6)
    News Clippings
  - 1982 Negotiations (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1199 History (1 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1199 History (2 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "My Brother's Keeper" Rev. Jesse Jackson's Speech to the World Jewish Congress, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    July 7, 1992 in Brussels, Belgium
  - 1199 Opinion/Editorial, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1199 - "The History of a Fighting Union" (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Feature Articles Regarding 1199, 1959-1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Local 1199 Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    January 1991
  - 1199 Articles, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 15)